FROM ME TO YOU
THE TWO
TO SAWAKO-CHAN
DON'T BE SURPRISED.
THIS WORLD HAS NO SANTA.
Uh...
It was real!
All of it was real!
Morning, Dad...
Th... Thank you.
Sawako... it must've been such a shock. I'm
sure it's hard to wrap your head around.
Even if you know the present was from
your old man, would it still make you
- happy? Sawako!
- She already left to
- get the newspaper, dear.
- My baby girl. My--
Today is the 25th of December.
And our closing ceremony.
Man, were you guys as
shocked as I was yesterday?!
Yeah.
Sadako, right?
Uh-huh. at karaoke she just appeared.
Wicked, they are cast
away daughters of the night.
Yoshida and Yano handed her the mic,
she sang one song, and left in an instant,
- just like that!
- Hold up. I thought she had come
with Kazehaya, or am I losing it?
- No, I was thinking that too.
- Yeah, but no matter what it
- seems like, there's no way-- Huh?
- You guys are all idiots.
I'm the one who got Sawako to go. And
yesterday I destroyed Kazehaya in a game,
so as punishment, I
made him wait for her.
I mean, she didn't know
where the after-party was at, so...
- Ah, I see!
- So, that's why!
Not yet. There're still a lot of juicy
events coming up, including Valentine's.
Can't have you dumb dumbs
interfering and ruining everything.
Punishment, huh?
- Why am I getting the chills?
- But Sawako's not even at that point yet.
And if things goes wrong, She might
start worrying about "Kazehaya's
- reputation" again.
- M-Morning.
- Makes sense Don't you think? M-Morning.
My classmates are returning my greetings!
Kazehaya!
- You're sure early!
- Yeah, so what? I'm always early... wha...
Since when?
It's a belly warmer.
I uh... crocheted it myself
but I made it for my dad, so...
I see... so it's not for me then.
Well, there was some confusion, and it
got swapped with what I was going to give
you. -Um, I don't want it to go to
waste, so if you don't mind, maybe give it
to your dad or mom or grandpa so they can
use it-- -But I can keep it for myself,
can't I?
Thanks a lot.
He's way too kind!
I doubt he'll ever wear something like
that, but he still accepted it with a
smile. Then again... he probably
wouldn't have worn that hat I made either.
So after all... I'm sure it wouldn't
have mattered which one I gave him.
Morning.
M-Morning.
But still, it does matter to me. Since
the feelings I put into each of them are
- different.
- That weather's really somethin', huh?
Your tie.
Ah, it's for the closing ceremony today.
Just when I thought he
couldn't glow any brighter...
Hey, guys!
- Oh, good morning, Chizu.
- Morning, Sawa.
- Morning.
Morning, Yano-chin, Kazehaya.
It's freezing out and
you are this energetic?!
That's right, our closing ceremony.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll be on winter break.
I think I may be a little lonely.
Hi there! It's good to see everyone!
- Who's that?
- You're in the way. Move it.
- Zen?!
- It's Zen!
- Our teacher! From homeroom!
Been so long!
Uhm, I know this is sudden, but...
I have decided to take over my in-laws'
sake brewery. And as such, today will be
my last as homeroom teacher.
- So, what's going on?
- Weren't you sick? And it was bad, right?
- Sick?
- Well, we heard you had
a string of bad luck.
No, business is booming at our sake
brewery, and I'm also getting along great
with my wife's family.
- Well, I wasn't expecting that...
- Mr. Arai...
We should celebrate! What'd you say?
Oh, thank you! But, unfortunately, I have
to hurry on home. I won't ever forget the
days I spent with this class!
Zen...
If you really wanna have a party
celebrate me being your new teacher. yeah?
Um, today is the closing
ceremony, so let's line up.
Hey, it's single file!
What an exciting second term...
Even her "blegh!" Is cute!
- It certainly wasn't boring.
- Uh, this marks the start of your winter
break, but make sure to be on your best
behavior...
And please take good care of yourselves
in your time away, so that you may welcome
- the new year in tip top shape...
- Honestly, I can't
believe how much has happened.
There were some tough moments, but they
feel like nothing... compared to the many
happy ones.
Um... this is a goodbye
card from all of us.
K-Kuronuma?!
You'll be fine. She's
actually an exorcist.
All rise!
- I may not look any different than before...
- Bow.
But these past few months, I've
experienced so many things for the first
- time.
- Alright! Winter break starts tomorrow!
- Hey, hey! Let's drop by somewhere to eat!
- Yeah, sure.
Where do you wanna go?
Kazehaya!
Karaoke! Let's go!
We just went yesterday.
Once I go home... I won't be able to see
him... until we're back for the third term.
"Thank you for everything this year."
"Because of you, it
was really, really fun."
Kazehaya, come on!
He's leaving! J-just make it quick, um...
Yeah.
See ya!
Uh... happy new year.
I'll see you next year.
Your dad did a good job! Did you
set up your email address yet?
Well-I, I haven't read the
entire instruction manual.
The whole thing?
You don't have to do that.
C'mon, give me the
phone. I can do it for ya.
Please. Thank you.
- What do you want it to be?
- Uhm...
It's better you make it a long address,
so you won't get as much junk mail. Like,
- your full name or birthday.
- U-Uhh...
EMAIL ADDRESS
Oh wow! No one will misunderstand now!
Hold up. You mean New
Year's Eve is your birthday?
Y-Yeah.
Chizu, Ayane, um...
I was wondering, maybe we can meet
during the break? Like when you're bored?
I mean so super bored?
Only if you'd like to, that is...
Don't be silly. Of
course we can all hang out!
I'm surprised that after all we've
been through, you'd still say that.
Plus, now it'll be way
easier to stay in contact.
I don't have to wait until
the third term to see them!
Oh, so every year, Ryu and I go together
to visit the shrine on New Year's Eve. But
this year, what do the two of
you think about coming with us?
- Yeah, sure.
- I could see everyone on New
Year's Eve?! I want to go!
I... I...
I'm just gonna check really quickly.
- Wow!
Really? You'll go with
Chizu and Ayane? Sounds lovely.
You should check with your dad once
he gets home. He still feels bad about
yesterday, so I'm
certain he won't say no.
A-Alright! I'm in!
- Yesterday, she must've been...
... We'll be together on New Year's Eve.
That means, on my 16th
birthday, I get to be with everyone.
Sawako, did you get to
trade numbers with Kazehaya yet?
Uh... We did it when I saw him yesterday.
- So did you use it yet?
- No, I haven't had a reason.
You do now, don't you?
Well, right now, it's the four of us--
you, me, Chizu and Ryu-- going to the
shrine together. If
you're good with that... great.
But if you want to see Kazehaya too,
you're gonna have to invite him yourself,
Okay?
Invite him?!
And if you don't contact him ASAP,
his schedule's bound to fill up fast.
I'm not gonna force you or
anything. But if you wanna see him. Yeah...
If I don't reach out to him now, then... I
won't see him again until the third term.
I... I don't know how to write text
messages yet, so I'll call him.
Hello. It's Kuronuma.
Visting the shrine on
on New Year's Eve... so...
Breathe, girl!
- this is making me nervous too.
If I got to see him, I'd feel so lucky...
It would make me very very happy.
Do your best.
Don't-- don't-- don't-- don't-- don't
you say a thing! You should turn away and
rethink your play.
- Hello?
- T-This is... K-Kuronuma!
I-I was wondering if you'd like to go to
the shrine... for New Year's Eve at
midnight?
It'll be with Chizu, Ayane, and Sanada
too. You're free. Oops. I mean, if you're
free...
I'll go!
So, Yoshida, Yano and Ryu... and you right?
- I promise I won't get in the way!
- I'll go.
Looking forward to it.
H- He's looking forward to it!
- Nice going.
- Not surprised.
I get to see him. And on
my birthday of all days...
I'll see him!
- Now then...
Let's see...
It's like I'm dreaming.
The days flew by... and before I knew it,
and it was December 31st, New Year's Eve.
Oh my, you don't need to worry about
cleaning up! They're coming to pick you up
soon, right? Chizu and Ayane?
That's right, and you shouldn't
keep your friends waiting for you.
O-Okay, thank you. I'll wear
the poncho you gave me too.
I see, so Sawako's going to
the shrine with friends now...
Wait, I know that Chizu and Ayane are my
friends now, but what about Sanada and
Kazehaya? Are they
considered my friends too?
Especially in Kazehaya's case...
We're here!
Good evening!
You came early.
Oh my, welcome.
Sorry to barge in!
- Wait here. I'll get my coat.
- Actually, can we come in for
a bit? And go to your room?
Oh, of course, come in.
H-Huh?
What're you doing to me?
- Hey, don't move!
- Uh... I'm sorry.
Don't worry, I'm going light. No one will
be able to tell you're wearing something.
Okay. Look down.
Like... this?
Now don't blink.
Remember how when you first met Kurumi,
you mentioned how you wanted to become
cuter? You have a reason for wanting
that, don't you? Think about what it is.
There. All done!
Almost finished. There, a
little gift from me and Yano-chin.
- Happy Birthday, Sawako!
- Cute! So cute!
- Totally! Man, we're good!
Yeah! Nice!
And that hairpin too!
- Thank you--
- Stop! Don't cry!
Hold it in! You have to!
They worked so hard on this... There's
no way I could ever let it go to waste!
With the makeup...
She's scarier.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Right now I'm really, really happy.
Since meeting you two this year, there've
been so many things that have made me feel
this way.
Now then.
The meetup spot's pretty close to
here. Shall we get going, Chizu?
Yeah, Sounds good.
Bye.
Yeah, we'll see ya later.
You have fun with Kazehaya, okay?
- Wait... where are you...
- Don't worry about us, 'cause we're
good! Oh and Ryu won't be joining you guys
either!
Wai...
- Oh, but you gotta share all the deets.
- What are you scared of?
You're the one who invited him.
Chizu and Ayane worked so hard to make me
look as cute as possible... for this moment,
right now.
Ryu's not here yet. Are
the girls on their way?
They're not.
Sanada's not coming... either.
Is he disappointed about that?
Is he upset? Will he leave?
Well... let's go, then.
It's the 31st of December.
In thirty minutes, the New Year begins...
An exchange of words...
On a night with moonlit snow...
Next time: "Birthday."